[Music]
hello
is this good qualities
oh good good good I'm glad I'm glad no
potato quality I'm on a brand new iPhone
11 Pro here good quality all right good
good good good is what I like to hear
all right we got some tea and we got
some Lacroix and I'm in my brand new
office so as promised while we wait for
everybody to come in here and join our
our amazing coalition of people who are
definitely gonna smack the Buy button on
this product you know you know like I it
is it is really good it is it is a
really good product
I wouldn't know this isn't common prime
this products really good um come on
friends okay common friends okay common
phone is getting better you know common
friend but but this one this one is is
is months in the making
we're gonna show you some really cool
stuff today um I found a quote that was
really inspirational Oh
so I wanted to share that with you guys
it's this quote right here and I'm not
sure if it's backwards its first they
ignore you then they laugh at you then
they try to copy you then you change the
world and that quotes by Elizabeth
Holmes so you know I thought I thought
that quote was really inspirational so
let's let's go live
live Spain now
yeah I know I'm on a different Street
from the scheduled one I know why wait
I'm watching myself but it's backwards
its backwards on the screen it's
backwards on the screen you can't see it
yeah yeah Elizabeth Holmes you're a
chill driver from Switzerland welcome to
the stream welcome to the stream we got
35 people come in join our broad
coalition of great people in the
community we're definitely gonna smack
the Buy button on this product it's
really no it's not no no no no don't you
know whoa let's go let's go fifty-two
let's go let's go at 3:00 p.m. we are
gonna open the bag you see the bag we're
gonna open the bag at 3:00 p.m.
here's my yawn
this is running open pilot zero point
six point five um you can check out the
beautiful new home screen yeah oh it's
just I don't know final incoming eyes
YouTube
I posted them on this uh yeah no don't
worry I haven't unveiled the product yet
I'm wait until three yeah if there's no
product unveiling we're doing an office
tour and you can see this top one here
and Nabal open violet so if you have the
new hardware this toggle will work if
you don't have the new hardware you're
gonna have to flip switches so there's
that um buy new hardware all right good
no I didn't what does no new hardware I
didn't jump the gun into a shed then do
it alright alright let's go
can we ask about self-driving cars in
here absolutely this is finally the
place to do it
you want a tour of common we're gonna go
on a tour we're gonna go on a tour but
first for everyone who hasn't seen no no
I promised the new harbor is not
canceled we built a lot of them is
really good my Elizabeth Holmes quote up
the name of the heart ran well we can't
show you that well that's a secret all
right all right
yes we're finding something out today at
3 o'clock that's a 3 p.m. so in five
minutes we're gonna open this bag up
we're gonna open this bag and we're
gonna see the new hardware and this is a
neon this is our old hardware I'll tell
you guys early spoiler 217 people thank
you all for joining this Eon is not
going away
eons are still as relevant as they ever
were but what's in this bag is gonna
make your Eon way better so at 3 p.m.
we'll be opening the bag to be like you
know going into this bag we'll be
pulling things out of the bag and we'll
be showing them to you guys we have a
medium post we got we got some great
stuff coming and I believe shops gonna
get updated too right away at 3 p.m. so
you don't even have to listen to me talk
you can just smack that Buy button as
soon as it goes live huh Jack died my
chat die wait what a chat for what a
chat break chat disconnected this is
terrible YouTube oh yeah no no we're
good we're good we're good
oh yeah all your chats back alright
let's do it let's do it got 245 people
get everybody in here 248 248 and we're
gonna be in just four minutes reaching
into this bag and looking at the latest
Hardware of common AI let me just remind
myself what it oh that's that's pretty
nice
what's that's a nice wow that's that's
pretty nice oh yeah that's that's good
that's good stop and see the sea yarn
it's not for sale alright but this is my
new office so you guys I hope you like
it I have my own office now these are my
books this is my television it's not
connected to anything yet this is my
couch so we go over here and we just
chill baby chill we wait for stuff we
talk to people yeah so that's my
office that's my whiteboard yeah my
Elizabeth Holmes quote I find it really
inspirational every time I think about
that I might be doing badly at startup I
just remembered the raw knows and I know
that I'm not doing badly that's because
we're making real money for real people
like you guys today where you're gonna
hit the Buy button on the car harness oh
whoa whoa I said the name of the product
oh I shouldn't have done that
that's a leak I get the black bear oh
yeah you'll give my ship in a black bag
don't like this one but but we're gonna
open this bag I'm gonna just reach in
here I'm gonna just can't show you the
product now is yes I got two minutes
yeah we're breaking YouTube we're
breaking YouTube all right
no no she lives in a San Francisco with
her with her new boyfriend and her wolf
dog that's what I heard
all right this is not an Elizabeth home
stream this is a comma a I stream where
we're announcing a new product in just
two minutes in just two minutes so stay
tuned here let's play the jeopardy music
that's what I like to do when I wait
jeopardy music all right let's go 30
second timer with Jeopardy
[Music]
alright guys we're going live in just a
few minutes no guys I'm actually this
isn't I'm actually psyched for this
product you guys it's good it's good I
wouldn't tell you if it was good if it
wasn't good umm it's it's it's really
it's not just it's not just oh what's in
the bag
we need 420 viewers yo you'll get people
in here call up your friends tell them
Commons if I have to reveal what's in
this bag in just 5 5 minutes about 5 min
how many minutes that I said I know
we're still getting people I think we
gotta wait I don't think we can do it at
exactly 3 I think we're gonna have to go
to a commercial break first ah look we
got we got T we got Lacroix mmm ok
oh it's live it's live I'm gonna shop is
it live on the shop I've on the shop you
go oh it's live on the shop it's live on
the shop okay at 3:00 p.m. okay let's go
let's open this bag up congratulations
welcome to our hardware future um we
also have a medium post let's just can
we go live with that as well
if you guys out there at comma watching
live team if you could just go live at
the video post so people can can read
along at home actually know what I can
do it right here but that's boring you
guys came here to watch me pull things
from the back so we're gonna start with
this here this is the car harness well
the whole thing's called the car harness
first of all but this wire is a
replacement for the giraffe so you see
we have different wires
Honda Bosch Toyota Honda Knight AK
instead of needing all that complexity
that used to be in a giraffe I don't
even have a giraffe I'll show you one
later they were terrible the giraffe was
the worst product comet ever made and I
really think that the car harnessed this
new product right now is the best so you
see this is a car harness on this side
we have a brand new connector we're
introducing right here this is obd see
it uses a USBC cable plugs right in
there like us this 26 pin connector is
open source will explain to you what it
is in the medium post but if you want to
add a new car to open pilot to the
common eco system you'll just have to
make a wire and these wires are super
easy to make this is all available on
digital I would just take the Toyota
wire I'd click it right in here to my
car harness like this and we're good to
go you'll see that there's another port
here - this is an Ethernet port it
connects with an Ethernet cable you know
i plug the ethernet cable in here got
together end Ethernet cable see how it's
flat it beautifully tucks into the trim
of your car and it connects to the comma
power v2 remember the terrible white
comma power super light really ugly this
is the replacement reliable and it
doesn't just have power it also has
can 424 viewers that's higher than the
price that Ilan was gonna take Tesla
private act let's go for 29 welcome
welcome for those you're just joining
the stream the product is called the car
harness oh yes and the most wonderful
thing that I didn't even talk to you
guys about this harness it's entirely
underneath your trim so you can take
this and in all of the supported cars
you buy the harness the correct one for
your car you'll be able know it's the
price a typo no way no way it's not
cheap you know this is quality stuff
[Laughter]
well we haven't gotten Dollard again
it's not just this we're still gonna
pull one more thing from the back but
yeah so this is a Toyota cable plug it
in here USBC cable , power v2 which
doesn't just do power it also does kin
so fingerprinting 2.0 is going to read
the VIN from the car so this will just
go in here like this and then you have a
complete set up where does this cable
connect you might ask to the greatest
part of the car harness it's this the
black panda the black panda has all the
great stuff from a grey panda this has a
high-precision GPS inside of it and I'm
gonna take you guys live to the
manufacturing oh we can go look at this
stuff
this has four can transceivers this is
the part you're paying for USB C plugs
in right here and of course you can take
an Ethernet cable USB in the USB cable
this is a commis maze also available for
sale in the shop plugs right in here or
you can just use a normal USB cable
you're gonna need this mains I just
don't have one and it plugs right in
here - you're here complete
this is the v2 hardware system are they
in stock and ready to ship well if you
order today and you're one of the first
50 people to order will ship it out on
Monday so yes they're in stock and ready
to ship and we're gonna go look at that
right now
this is a car varnas and maybe now we
can roll to the video that shows the
harness off is the medium post live no I
don't think it is
let's just go live with the medium post
here called our Hardware future that
just basically goes over what we talked
about and we're gonna watch a quick
video I'm gonna flip cameras so we can
watch this video yeah this is the
harnessed trailer yo I hope you guys
enjoy whoops
got to make sure we got sound yeah yeah
there we go wait let's rewind all of
this for the low low price of 399 if you
think it's high it's gonna go up so buy
today the black Panda the greatest Panda
calm a eyes ever made
[Music]
yeah um if you guys are enjoying videos
we also have a full v2 hardware
installation video linked from the
medium post shows you just how easy it
is to install but you guys can watch
that on your own okay let's look at the
inspirational Elizabeth Holmes quote for
a little bit that's good and now let's
go on a factory tour first we're gonna
take you to the left here our testing
closet this is the company's predictions
for how many car harnesses we're gonna
sell they range from 15 to 99 so please
get your order in today for our harness
that's live at shop tower comedy guy
this is our testing closet where we test
Aeons we've been testing car harnesses
now for over a month
this is the most well tested call
hardware that kamas ever shipped let me
see if I can bring the comments up here
so I can see them comments top chat live
chat oh yes here we go yes perfect
and now we're gonna take you guys live
to the factory floor where these
products are being made so you'll see we
have black pandas uncased right here
this is a black panda you'll see it
includes a GPS some can transceivers
there some can transceivers there and
upgraded inductor this is uh no more
power issues for your Yuans Corolla
hybrids are gonna be fixed with
fingerprinting 2.0 so this is what a
black panda looks like without a case
this is a GPS antenna it's already built
in to the complete black panda here so I
think if I open this guy up I don't to
break it these things are very expensive
it includes the GPS antenna so this is
everything wait it's flipping this is
everything that's in a gray panda just
in a much smaller case
this here is kama powers ready to ship
power V twos
these are car harnesses you can check
them out they're sort of beautiful no
scam it's all real it's all right here
for you today we can go down here we can
see all the wire so giraffes are being
discontinued powers are being
discontinued you need hardware too if
you have any questions about it you need
hardware to buy hardware to today oh
yeah check it out you only want it if
it's real that's right it is real this
is where I make it some more eons always
making some more eons these are called
powers without they're beautiful cases
if you want to write now you might be in
the first 50
I don't know how quick these sold these
are antennas yeah cool guys oh yeah
wait is that part of the oh we should
talk about that I thought there was only
four people who got the email Oh yo yo
if you guys buy a shirt with it it's
only three dollars yeah ninety percent
off I said it all wrong Wow someone
should have given me talking points for
this I'm worse than I'm worse than than
you know when those guys go on
late-night TV and don't know what
they're talking about
Oh 90% off get your t-shirt right now
that's crazy you already bought yours
well you know what it's great it's great
it's only 399 do we have anything we
want to show them oh we got something
special what do we got oh I don't
remember where are they
why we showed them the wires is it do I
know about this oh the boss one oh yeah
oh it's $30 but you got to use the promo
code shirt yo is that real plastic this
is a real Bosch connector no more 3d
printed they work great Bosch harness
Subaru harness and FCA harness coming
soon but for now everybody who has a
Honda night act a Honda Bosch Toyota it
does work in Russia make sure to buy one
cool wow we got 459 people here pedals
no we don't sell pedals but oh yeah by
the way if you just split the Ethernet
it'll work with a pedal it works
perfectly with the pedal just split the
Ethernet should we well so you know the
harness is cheap to make but the the
black pan does not so cheap black pandas
are great oh the discount code doesn't
work do you want to go to our sales team
and and complain mmm
hey Alex they say the discount code
doesn't work code works fine never mind
just didn't know how to use it yeah just
bought it all right should we see how
many were sold how do you get assured
for no more switches no more switches
yeah if your stuffs less than a month
old you can return it we have a 30-day
return policy on everything so if you'd
like to send back your giraffe and your
other Panda and it's been only 30 days
of course we honored the return policy
here yeah so giraffes powers pause pause
now paws are gone Oh paws are still here
no pause actually work with black pandas
two giraffes are over powers are over
pandas gray pandas look how many gray
pandas we have left that's right none
them because the black Panda is a far
superior product to the gray panda let's
go take another look at it if you return
it smash you don't get your money back
oh but yeah let's go take another look
at the black panda you know you might
think that you know because it's small
it's not powerful I promise you it's
powerful
there's no GM version uh right now
better USBC than Raspberry Pi for I oh
my
you guys you guys that's today's sales
oh I'm so happy you guys are applying
them oh this is incredible this is
incredible we made ten grand today yo
we're gonna break the record of 26 grand
or what 26 grand is the all-time ,
record oh man this product's a hit
that's right that's right
oh they're so nice they're really nice
they really are beautiful and if you're
one of the first 50 to buy you'll get it
shipped out on Monday
it's Kama pedal compatible you just need
to get an Ethernet splitter you just
need that one wire down super good
whoo 21 sales all right there's no new
functionality oh I didn't even tell you
guys about the functionality no there's
new functionality okay do you know about
cruise fault do you know when you have
to take your car and you have to power
cycle the car because it has a cruise
fault error because your Aeon was turned
off that doesn't happen anymore inside
of this harness is advanced relay
technology this is all fixed you can
unplug your Aeon and it just switches
right back to stock that is one of the
great things fixed on our Hardware v2
system also you see these little loop
wires right here no dip switches the
relays are not optically isolated
there's no reason to do that
um but it is advanced relay technology I
do promise um you have to add the shirt
to the car and thing to the car you
can't just get the shirt oh if that's
what you're trying to do you're cheating
you gotta buy a harness if you want to
get a 90% off shirt no crews fault
completely still this stuff fits
entirely inside your your trim too late
to get shirt well send us an email if
you send an email to support we'll add a
shirt on afterwards we did announce that
too late
that was because I'm the worst talk-show
host ever a Lima gonna thank you thank
you thank you 463 people everybody go
out there if you have an e on you buy a
black panda today comes with all of this
you're not gonna regret it you're gonna
love the way your car looks you're not
gonna lose that piece of plastic that
comes with the car because you can
reinstall everything on the car stock if
you pull the USBC cable out of your
black panda or if you pull the USB cable
out of your black pen if you pull either
one of these cables out your car will
revert to stuff there's also a toggle
added on zero point six point five that
can rien a ball
open pilot where you can switch to stock
right like that say you know your wife
drives a car your friend drives a car
you want to disable open pilot just
disable compile it right like that and
this Aeon will turn right to dashcam
mode check out the beautiful new screen
this of course ships to everybody if you
don't have come a crime and you live in
the US this is an ad for comma Prime we
love ads but if you buy a black panda
today you're getting with the hardware a
v2 program also if you have an old
Toyota giraffe well you'll see what the
problem is
you're probably gonna definitely want to
buy a harness um because you're gonna
get everything fixed up you're gonna get
your high beams back you're gonna get
you a TV back that's all gonna be fixed
oh man wait who said twenty one orders
you got way more than twenty one orders
we got a crazy amount of orders guys
look at what we're at right now we're at
12440 four dollars you guys right now
can help us break this record 26
thousand is the record from July 4th by
a black panda today you're getting with
the future I promise you prices are not
gonna go down prices only go up you know
I've been I've stuck to that he owns
have gone up white pandas have gone up
this is the cheapest you're gonna be
able to get a black panda for so make
sure if your
by one buy it today you're gonna love it
and you know it just gets you with the
new v2 hardware
notice that this thing is not called the
black Panda where the car horn is this
is called our Hardware future giraffes
and pandas were v1 Colome whoo Chris
thank you um what about Ford's IDs you
were no DSU I mean it works with both um
we just put a white fan of 2030 four
days ago here a little Oh any updates
yeah zero point six point five is going
out to develop I mean this stuff's all
cheap this stuff's wires but what you're
really binds a black panda right here
black panda has got an entire gray panda
fit in here
in addition to you know how hard it is
to make it so you can plug the cable in
this way or this way real hard but we
did it we did a great job with the
engineering of course all the code on
the black band is completely open-source
github.com such come any I slash panda
the real takeaways here are if you have
do the email go out did you guys get the
email um oh a on v2 and yeah yeah black
pant
that's where it's at alright let's see
let's see what we got let's see let's
see how many orders we got how are we
doing how we doing on sales have we here
oh one more salem we're gonna cross
13,000 one more sale we're changing the
game guys what this is doing what this
system really is what hardware v2 really
is this stuff you know the ethernet
cable you won't even see any of this all
that's gonna come out of your car is
this and this is a USBC cable we've
created a custom protocol for it called
obd see ODBC this is the future of
interfacing with your car this has four
can buses on it relay control and
started detection yeah we're gonna use
iphone 11 pros we are just like bit
connect except we're not a scam and if
you buy one of these will actually send
you something oh it's only 399
it is only to aetherium it's it's like
none of a Bitcoin I wish it was less
aetherium aetherium was worth more but
now you know you can't have everything
can it start the car well okay so the
other thing that this has that the old
stuff did not is so this is a common
power as you can see there's five pins
on here two grounds one power and to
camp so the black panda has four
canvases and the fourth canvas allows
you to talk to this the canvas on the
OBD so if your car has lock and unlock
support from from like the the tools
that it comes with like honda has hds
toyota has t is you couldn't if that
figure out what can come and was sent
and then you'll be able to unlock your
car live overcome a crime alright and
that's where this is going that's one of
the reasons we added the canvas here we
can also do fingerprinting 2.0 so for
the corolla hybrid for the honda clarity
there were a few cars that broke
fingerprinting 1.0 they're all gonna
work and fingerprinting 2.0 and you're
gonna need this hardware obd c obd see
why does car horn is a separate unit not
integrate into black panda this hides
underneath your trim this does not this
needs to be on the windshield cuz it has
a gps inside of it whoa whoa guys guys
what is that what does that say remember
when I thought we were getting a smash
the record we're gonna obliterate it
yo know if you haven't placed your or
yet 437 people get in right now I think
you will still be ok so so this is this
is real talk I'm not even making this up
I'll prove it to you 33 total orders the
next 17 people who order will be in the
first 50 and you'll get it on Monday
um if you order after that it'll ship
later that's how many we can make this
week we can make about 50 a week us PC
with can is odbc yes it is what is my
role at common today I am the president
I am the president
that means
I'm but I'm not like one of those
democratically elected presidents I'm
like one of those you know like like the
president of something that has a lot of
like Democratic and people's in the name
yeah that's that's what I'm president of
um so I am here today and I am obviously
telling you that this stuff is the
future of the comic ecosystem I was not
this hyped on the prime talk I was not
this I because we've been working on
this for like a long time now
we were gonna launch something similar
to this but not as good three months ago
and I just got mad and said this is this
is total crap we're gonna cancel that
and we're gonna do it well and this is
the one that's done well I will Ford be
in the ecosystem soon floored has a
ten-second lockout problem probably not
the new fusions I think we can add Ford
back in and it will be super easy to
just design a new twenty six pin cable
that works with Ford John dies so if you
buy the coma harness um we can ship you
send an email to support about it we'll
ship you one of these with just wires so
you'll have to get the connectors for
the car yourself but it's fairly
Universal actually looking at that post
on the medium post is pretty good so
let's just let's just turn around here
and take a look at this so this is the
pin outs of the cable um so this this is
this cable right here faces like this um
so this is what you'll need to wire up
your own car most cars are wired like
this the car connects to the camera
connects to the radar so you can just
wire it up like that
it's pretty easy if you've done a
carport nissan rogue support coming VW
coming yeah I mean what this is allowing
us to do Hyundai is actually in official
open pilot right now we're gonna try to
make you and I dongles I'm gonna try to
make these for Hyundai right now we've
just made the three most common but
uh-oh yeah and these are all the we're
gonna open source the wiring diagrams
for these we want to make it easy for
people to add new cars to our ecosystem
the camera shaking sorry
GM GM's coming
Nissan Rogue yes absolutely yeah third
party can absolutely make these wires
and sell them yeah my happy hacking
keyboards beautiful eyelets
Oh Mongo guys guys 15700 36th only 14
more people are gonna get in yo well i
autographed the first 50 hundred no I'm
not willing to sell myself out like that
you got up some standards but I will
appreciate you and love you forever
whatever that means
black panda coke dude I sniff you know
you know some people are excited about
black pandas I've been working on this
for three months post shop info on
Twitter yeah we closed the shop info on
on Twitter we also post that
installation video on Twitter if you
guys are out there listening oh I guess
well you there waiting for the live
stream to be over but yeah yeah let's
start let's start posting that stuff um
what T am i drinking it's green green
tea I don't know my friend made it for
me um the clarity will be officially
supported I believe I think the clarity
is only problem is fingerprinting the
comma power is included and yes it's
required no we're not clearing out we're
actually almost out of stock of gray
pandas how much longer will the OGE on
work in the comic ecosystem for a while
for a while when i planet deprecated
that anytime soon what will be
deprecated first is white pandas and
giraffes and gray pandas right now
there's no reason for us to break them
but once fingerprinting 1.0 becomes too
hard to maintain future versions of open
pilot are only gonna work with the black
panda and only gonna work with
fingerprinting 2.0 um no so this
actually has a built-in gps antenna
already um by the way i've been working
on this the company's been working on
this for three months when you actually
make a product nice
we have installation videos it takes a
lot of time how are we decoding the VIN
we're building a big lookup table we do
ship to Sweden we ship worldwide gotta
pay for shipping free shipping in the
u.s. though so if you're in the US get
in right now get your free shipping
we gonna smash the sales record live on
this stream we're up to seventeen
thousand six hundred and fifty eight
dollars if we get that above twenty six
you guys are setting the all-time
one-day sales record for koumei I will
there be updates to the porting guide
it doesn't change that much
fingerprinting that the whole notion of
fingerprinting and having to add a
fingerprint is gonna go away with the
black Panda and fingerprinting 2.0 and
we're gonna build that on the server
side yeah I know that hockey stick right
well who was buying anything today when
the new product was coming out at 3:00
right that's like somebody who buys the
iPhone X the morning the iPhone 11 comes
out um the new Jeep Wrangler I believe
so I think that the jeeps are supported
we're gonna do FCA dongles pretty soon
we're gonna roll out FCA dongle and
Subaru dongle next um yeah you need to
buy more Toyota's what's the code the
code is shirt if you just put in shirt
you can get a three dollar shirt that's
ninety percent off on shirts that's the
cheapest shirt you can't even buy shirts
from street vendors in New York for that
cheap can we just spin he's been
spamming scam I mean you know not
everybody can be helped uh he said VW
coming yeah yeah we're doing we're doing
VW I know you need more torts we've been
talking about the cork situation we know
and actually if there's ever any
firmware updates see they can be pushed
right here through this obd you can
using the fourth cam available only on
black panel all their pandas only had
three cans black panda is the first with
before cams
that's one more cam what about that
conversation about cooling the EON well
you know now it's easy to take the eon
off when you take the eon down it's not
gonna cause any loose fault problems on
your car it's really easy all the link
is on twitter the link is on twitter
comic our harnesses are available now
let's we got we got some great video
content too we did uh yeah it's one more
cat you know promo code today so the
promo code guys i'm gonna paste it right
here is
shirt is 90% off shirt with black with
car harness purchase yeah have you ever
thought about working for the Chinese
government no Mazda is also happening
yeah no great job mmm I wish I
remembered his name but there's someone
who discord have been working really
hard on the Mazda 4 we really want to
get that upstream it's incredible how
far this community has grown in the last
limit let me let me shout out when he
shout out the Mazda 4 I think we've
gotten that already up streamed into
Panda and that's Mazda Jafar yes Jafar
all he's been he's been working on the
Mazda and it looks really good and
shout-out to Angela for making my office
beautiful can we link her can we link
her can we can we give love to everybody
what car should we select for other cars
um we should have launched with that we
should have launched with that I'm sorry
we didn't that'll be up in a bit
don't buy back the cathode is the next
evoke recently right guys we're winning
we're winning key is it's all coming all
the other cars are coming it's gonna be
so easy for us because the harness is
the same for all cars the black panda
the same for all cars power the same for
all cars the only thing that changes is
these and we're gonna get lots of
different ones that I made if Eon is
dead yes it'll automatically switch if
your Eon is dead it'll automatically
split from stock you don't have to shut
the car off this will just automatically
happen Dodge Challenger probably not
eighties Volvo oh yeah we've left that
in Vegas with some guy who tried to give
us Walmart gift cards for Real Talk , is
yes we're gonna go for an hour with this
stream so if anybody has any questions
I'm happy to talk about the comedy
ecosystem and really this someone said
it I mean all our future products are
gonna work with this same obd seek and
there that works on the black panda so
it's gonna be the same connector it's
gonna be the same harness you're only
ever gonna have to take your trim off
once no it's not USBC power delivery
protocol it's we put 12 volts on the
USBC don't plug this into a phone it's
actually pretty safe in most phones but
don't plug it into a phone I'm how good
is comma Prime is it really worth it
well it is exactly what it is you have
to make your own decision about whether
it's worth it some people really think
it is um black panda definitely worth it
come a prime also big feature coming
next year like an unreal feature so you
know you can always you can always hold
off till next year when we up the price
you'll have to pay more per month but
you know the new Panda has hired a
powerup but yeah um so it has a it
hasn't much better switching power
supply brilliant new hardware engineer
routed it for us it's good uh I soldered
her and that's what I like the
black pandas let's see what the sales
are up to yo yo we're gonna smash that
record we're gonna smash that record you
can still get in right now and be one of
the first 50 we got 47 orders today
if I'm crying right now I mean no it's
it's useful it's it's unlimited a that
we fixed tethering in in zero point six
point five we are adding a new feature
soon gonna be snapshots you're gonna be
able to take a picture from your Aeon
right from the app we're making the app
like more interoperable with common
prime who's winning the bat in the
office well we already have some losers
as to who's gonna win I don't know but
we can go look at that board let's go
let's go back to the testing closet and
take a look at that losses um where's
that with the marker gotta go find the
marker let's go get a marker what oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah Harold has it down
here guessing um 15 we're just gonna
cross that one off Andy with 27 that can
go up 42 can go 32 can go 37 can go all
right all right all right so we got viv
right now we got Willem with 55 I guess
69 guys I'm just I'm just
I guess 69 and we got way Shing here
with 77 and we got Greg down here with
99 so will it be there with 47 that's if
nobody else buys one will it be willing
with 55 will it be me with 69 we'll be
waiting with 77 or will it be Greg with
99 yo let's see how many result ETA to
profitability our estimate actually was
selling 50 of these
so we've already crushed that estimate
I'm super happy with all of you
well we're hoping also 0.7 on software
coming to all the eons is gonna be
really good
0.6 did wonders for our sales our
revenue growth is up 50% from q2 to q3
we'vewe've 50% opt our revenue if we do
50% again in q4 a profitable company
0.65 0.65 is it in devel let me check
0.65 is not in developing a why but uh
coming soon a Comi UPS firmware might
happen uh we'll see
car horns is at 43 well oh it's at 43 or
what about the other ones no we've
already sold 7 them right those ones
aren't included but those ones aren't
included in the first 50 that are gonna
ship so if you get your order in right
now when are you gonna get a consumer
product so consumer products are journey
not a destination if Apple called the
iPhone a consumer product and said it
was over uh it'd be over but Apple
worked tirelessly to make eleven iPhones
and that's how many aeons we're gonna
have to make but the final one's gonna
drive your car right full self-driving
um what car should you buy for kamma
toyota corolla toyota corolla is the
best car it does work in the UK driving
on the left China I know it does
actually there's some great people
privacy policy
Commodore a / terms I believe it's
linked from the set up a boat of the app
which you can download for free so
that's probably the best place to lock
but if you're asking that question yeah
um we sense flow oh you wanna see the
data center let's go to the data center
guys we're just gonna take we're gonna
take this black panda with us in my
pocket so we can we can see the black
panda everywhere let's go to the data
center the data centers really cool we
do our training in-house because the
cloud is an overpriced camp so we're
just gonna bring you guys over here like
this so we're gonna see a few cool
things as we enter the cama garage
it's loud in here we got a rav4 you can
see ignore the terrible looking white
table but that's a black Panda right
there on the windshield beautiful setup
we've been testing them for months
here's our wall of printers where
everything is printed
and here is our data center I'm very
proud of it Greg's worked super hard on
it all of this is our data Wow
two of them are broken and these here
are forty 1080i GPUs these are our
random server computers and this is our
working data storage yes if someone
parks badly that's the end of the data
center in the printers it's true that's
why we have open pilot we have secret
good open pilot that does parking for us
check it out black panda cases beautiful
[Music]
stock ad with harness yes unless you
unplugged your DSU or I have a GM
without an SEM there were all Linux
simulators coming along great yeah it
does right and show you guys the secret
code oh you guys want to see look at
that fan a clouds a scam oh man well
that's sketchy don't touch it don't
touch it
behind the door wires and a big fan oh
my god that's the hell is sketchy
if you're concerned about privacy and I
mean your data is here look at them
blinking they look beautiful
no no we're in San Diego now just bought
all right that's what I like to hear
all right we got we got 14 more minutes
of the live stream do we record audio at
all no not at all and the front camera
is opt-in so by default we don't record
the front camera either oh yeah we got
it we got good locks and we got theft
insurance
I hate crime and that's why you moved to
San Diego because a lot less crime here
in San Francisco check it out we're
building some new yawns these are
actually gonna be throwback eons we're
gonna do some some og eons 128 gigabyte
we got the last stock of the one plazas
Toronto was less crime yeah but it's in
Canada it's cold black pandas open
source no the hardware's not open source
did we pass 25k let's go check oh yes
Python 3 on 0 6 5 so we're really moving
to the future wide my mind change on the
firmware there was yeah I don't know
some of you might know some of you might
be able to figure Oh will gain a break
the record today we're gonna break the
record I actually think that we can
subtract some of those were yawn orders
so you might still get in the first 50
if you go today rip stream no no
connection come back No uh can you make
a legal request to receive and download
all your data and you can try this is
why we've started deleting data its back
excellent excellent
we're at $23,000 guys I'm gonna stick
you know what I said it was gonna be an
hour but I'm gonna stick with the stream
until we smash the record let me let me
get I posted what the exact record was
in staff yesterday
in our slack let's see what it is no I
actually didn't post it because I was
concerned we weren't gonna break it but
now I know that we are so let's go look
at the end whoa we're looking at it I
got I can show you a video of
installation
[Music]
23700 $740 sister what's up yeah yeah if
they got an impatience and they wanted
then yeah I'm cool with that yeah you
gotta yeah you gotta give the t-shirt
size too
yes oh yeah oh yeah 22000 24266 whoa if
you buy it now you get an FCA connector
later wait till the FCA connectors ready
no our investors are not pressuring me
to make money
definitely not I'm pressuring everybody
to make money because if we make money
we prove that the idea is great and we
hire more people we get better models
you know money guys look at me we're
gonna we're gonna flip around and then
we're gonna do a look at me we're almost
at 69 now we just moved down here we
moved to a beautiful new office can't
invest not looking to raise money
[Music]
Zor tracks em to hundreds pick me back
to read the code don't think so
unless they snuck past me stick a sturdy
box International shipping purchase is
really hard investment to the company I
do live in San Diego I live in a
beautiful apartment watch me on twitch
if you wanna see it's super easy to set
up
[Music]
that clouds not a scam
it doesn't matter that much the GPS is
only good to a meter so thank you
uh yeah we don't know yeah he knows talk
to private company but I'll say that's
look all the money we make
so someone someone wants I think it was
a youtube comment where it was like you
know about me like this guy wants to be
a billionaire so bad well what I do with
a billion dollars well buy ya know every
dollar that , AI makes just goes back
into the company right like there's no
people taking profit off of the table if
we make more money we're a 13-person
company now you know why we're not a
huge company like like like tzuke's
and like cruise because those companies
lose billions of dollars every year
we're not only gonna win self-driving
cars we're gonna do it with a profitable
company um we're gonna sell stuff that
actually provides value to you if I
didn't think open pilot Act I'm thinking
about getting a new car I don't want to
get Toyota I don't want to get a Honda
but I don't know if I could get a car
without open pilot is it Toyota Corolla
with open pilot better than an Audi a4 I
think it is um take my shirt off whoo if
we get the 69 I mean how many hours a
day do we work yeah what'swhat's the no
we work normal schedules grow roll the
life have some basic Carver 1k I'd buy
that yes I still work a comma yes um a
Camry with open paws that in the name
for I really think that's true and that
just says like you're really getting
this product for so cheap compared to
the value that it adds we're gonna cross
25,000 soon we're at twenty four six six
eight there's three payments to capture
well I think those are the people who
bought shirts
wait unfulfilled what why oh I don't
know
26000 guys you guys we might even do it
in the hour this is insane
how do I cover my personal expenses I'll
tell you my salary I make $80,000 a year
that's legit my salary oh yeah yeah we
might run out of t-shirts so if you want
a t-shirt
yeah you better you better get it now
what's the no free lunch theorem you can
google it well no no free lunch in
search and optimisation we're talking
about that today at lunch yeah the
company pays my salary of course but
like I'm saying like I'm not taking
millions off the table here right
actually I below a salary at the company
now um some people got raises recently
so now I mean you know
how do you get I've I have personal
money I have other money too not related
to comma I make money streaming on
twitch twitch deep got TV slash George
Hotz and soon I'm gonna be an Instagram
influencer and then I'm gonna make buku
bucks and I'm gonna buy a yacht just
kidding no I'm not CEO I'm president if
you if you come to work here
you'll get salary choices and the lowest
one is eight again Tom if you want the
highest equity we do pay inequity yeah
so actually really the only way to
invest in comma the only way to get
common equity now is to come work here
nope no CEO can you work there as a
mascot you see if we sold two hundred
thousand dollars of sales today maybe
then we could afford a mascot I'm the
discount code for ninety percent off of
a shirt is shirt oh yeah I could make
two hundred k plus yeah beforeand okay
um but look I don't even know what I do
with money man whatever and then wait my
wins that's no fun we live in a fun
world what I look for an engineer's you
know knowing everything um we don't
really do like we develop open pilot
right we're not looking to make sketch
business deals we sell this like it's
foreign dollars you see exactly what it
is
we're totally transparent about it
where's open sources we can be why can't
see a knock anything it because there's
four canvases on here um plus power plus
ground so that's ten pins plus star
detect plus relay trigger so it's twelve
pounds you got a twelfth anything that
lying around somewhere Ethan it's a pro
tip guys we just broke the record we
just broke the record
highest sales day in common AI has yeah
yeah so we really are gonna be done Wow
we're gonna be done we're gonna be done
in an hour so it's gonna be an hour long
stream firstly Chris thank you do we
have anything else to do I think we
broke the record I think we only got
three more minutes road to 30k guys I'm
happy about the record we sold a lot and
I think 69 might be pretty Clutton I
think ratchet I saw a little more can I
live stream the celebration tonight
maybe yeah what higher we're actually
we're hiring for two positions right now
we're hiring an open pilot developer I'm
hiring a research engineer I'm so open
pilot developer we're looking for
someone with assistive background Python
background I'm someone who's really
gonna make open pilot super stable wants
to work on testing we're also hiring a
research engineer to work on the desire
problem um so if you guys read the open
pilot code and look at desire especially
people are writing Forks you might be
very interested in what that is desire
is one of the craziest things we're
doing here and it's really a big step on
our way to do self driving I can't say
full self-drive we build levels to a
tower systems show books
I'll show one book so I'll show one book
let's make a good book
yeah yes
information theory inference and
learning algorithms super important
stuff to know this is cool to home graph
complexity we're talking about this at
lunch this has to do with no free lunch
stuff twenty seven thousand three
hundred and three dollars give me a job
coming down AI that's where you apply um
smart Salman is a gimmick you don't want
that will do red lights and stop signs
before we do smarts on the cut out that
uh is everyone making the same effective
calm poll if you got an earlier you've
got more equity some people opted for
higher salaries some people opted for
higher equities it's pretty fair oh did
I just show for that book I don't make
any money off those books actually the
information during book is free as well
I bought just to support the guy I like
the author he's dead now though so I
don't want to support him anymore
will you get rich working you're coming
if you're coming here to get rich you
probably won't fit in well you might
though but if that's your goal go work
and Finance breath you'll make more
money in finance you really well but you
know you won't change the world
and grow slowly prisoner of resources
and wait for all the companies to crash
next year oh oh you need to raise 1.3
billion dollars to keep your company
around bro see I'm just happy making
mine making mine
twenty seven thousand three hundred
dollars today thank you to everybody who
some days I leave work smiling some days
they don't it depends if it works today
I'm gonna leave work smiling cuz we
broke the record whoo
it's common profitably got q4 this year
we're going for it hopefully hopefully
we saw 50 percent growth from q2 q3
we're hoping for another 50 percent
growth q3 too cute for and this starts
with the harness and the black Panda I
mean records not broken yet you mean of
course the records broken
I just sold another 120 7705 how does
the black pan to interact with the
Toyota TSU if you ever EDS you
disconnected the stock mode toggle won't
work unfortunately follow distance
reduction you don't yeah wait for end to
end longitudinal do I think being open
source will make it hard to compete with
other companies with significant capital
I think a lot of those companies are
just throwing capital away
they are absolutely throwing capital
away there are companies who are so much
better funded than us that have code
that's worse than open pilot we do take
interns we take interns year-round it's
a three month internship program again
the talent bar is quite high but if you
have a good github you have a good like
math and physics background will
absolutely take you as an attorney sales
are good but how many could be returns
we get a lot of returns lower than the
industry I think I were returning it was
like 5% um once people get open pilots
set up in their car and no one returns
it um how do I get a merge request
approved you mean a poor first kamidana
we're pretty good oh that was mistaken
the record has been broken guys the
record has been broken and then
longitudinal next year we'll ship to the
Aeons but let's first you know zero
point six point five should be in de val
any minute now I'm not sure why it's not
I'll find that out as soon as we stop
the stream allied our math company is
this someone's it for a sad reckoning um
except your pull request with the Subaru
we're gonna get serious about Subaru
when we ship the Subaru connector um
what happens with he owns right now we
make more eons
always more eons now an unexplained
antenna longitudinal no that'll be for
another day we don't exactly know how it
works yet we've been trying some very
basic experiments right now
sup J ROCs we make DI yeah you can make
DIY connectors we've we've checked the
medium post you check the medium post it
shows you how to do we work more than 40
hour weeks
yeah probably probably most people end
up but it's not none of its required
which hill it's a real chill place to
work you deadlines be smart that's it
it's nothing goes worked for a while
depending any car flex right yep I have
to come from the community there's not
enough most cars on the common network
are Toyota's well we have to do
marketing define marketing is anything
we did today marketing I'm okay with
everything we did today if you're
talking about and I'd love to buy a
Super Bowl ad man this guy on the Super
Bowl that'd be crazy uh
quantum supremacy I've seen that talked
about a bit lately just come and make
profit q4 we should be profitable no I
don't think other companies are aware of
what we've accomplished at all I think
if they really knew how our models
worked it's unreal how far ahead it is
um you know what Tesla's doted Joe is
that they talked about I think it's what
we already have um about CNN oh yeah we
need confidence yeah Joe Rogan known
about Nora
six minutes how does open pilot handle
uncertain traffic situation it hasn't
seen before the new model is trained on
so much driving it's trained on tons and
tons of driving
do I think way mo is a good company it's
not that way mo is a bad company they're
just extremely overvalued we pitched to
investors one said not at the current
not at the valuation I wanted of course
I just demanded a ram evaluation off the
top of my head the others said
absolutely there a 16z and we went with
them oh they're great
they're diggin they're good our partners
Chris dicks in there it's good guy as
you're talking to that yeah
I will say this if I ever go on Joe
Rogan and he offers me some weed I will
smoke is deep route a copy of open
violet I don't even know what deep route
is I really parking sensors now , prime
what is it
check the medium polish plan for lane
lines you were doing away with lane
lines tons of driving equals supervised
learning why are you so against
marketing a lot of it's really scummy
if not scummy I'm cool with it how many
people got the email by the way I think
we worked hard on that I'm pretty happy
with it I originally wanted to make the
subject re kangaroo what I think of deep
sky like position was it NACA higher
test actually I think publish that to
make it clear that Tesla doesn't acquire
companies for overpriced yeah paying for
market in 2019 is not my grades uh you
didn't get the email because you guys
bought eons I think a long time ago oh
you got the email right someone got the
email ID excellent um gonna need a good
jingle twenty-eight thousand one hundred
and ten dollars mr. Maira thank you
you bought yours less than a month ago I
don't know maybe you didn't opt into
emails well we'll have to figure it out
a gray panda more recently do you guys
lose
scale the io2 label stuff we got like
seven things labeled with them it's too
expensive it's too expensive to get like
10,000 images labeled would be $60,000
and that's more than we can really pay
if they lower their prices 10x if they
figured out how to do that like they got
it to work with models we'd uh we'd use
them
I do enjoy San Diego in San Francisco I
think San Francisco's an overhyped scam
do I think test will get to level 5
automation next year no no and I will
bet big money that they do not it's not
to say that I actually think test was
the farthest along but if anybody would
like to bat the test little knock it to
level 5 in 2020 if you like to bet that
they would I'll take the other side of
that bet
labeling in China should be cheap well
in China is not even the place for cheap
labor anymore China's crazy expensive
though did I really sell my soul
I say I say when did we get comment and
sure
earns Oh in a while we didn't work with
via walk so we didn't work with via and
that's the wonderful thing about open
pilot we didn't know that was coming
either guys this isn't about
partnerships this isn't about sketchy
backroom deals it's my shirt on inside I
think so um this is about MIT license
code that anybody can use oh well they
have we helped with the app yeah they
used our code they used our MIT license
code just like pronto used our gray
panda right like it's it's it's uh it's
not talking to us it's reading our
github I absolutely agree with what you
learned said about liner yes anyone
using lidar is doomed two minutes guys
no one will have it by 2025 that bet I
wouldn't take 20 20 I would take I'm not
saying I think it will be but I wouldn't
take it that um are there any
restrictions to using MIT license code
basically you can't sue us if it's
shitty that's basically it
um how many sales seventy seventy well
let's let's actually check so we sold
seven impatience um and then we can
check how many car harnesses we sold oh
there's three different types of car
harness
I think the bet goes until 3 p.m.
tomorrow I think Greg with 99 is
definitely gonna win thoughts on deep
scale I don't know much about forest a
few times I think they're pretty legit
if Tesla didn't pay an exorbitant price
for them and it's probably good deal I'm
no comments on the EPS firma right now
well adjustable follow distance ever
come to stock Opie no probably not
when will the next batch ship when we're
done making them won't be too long it
should be like 1 to 2 weeks should be
actually it should be within it it
should be a week after Monday I think we
can make like 50 a week can you remove
the liability with the EPS firmware the
prom with the EPS firmware as it can be
dangerous it can be dangerous so we are
looking into it I understand I put I on
flashed the torque mod from this deck
and it was terrible so I get it again um
no adjustable following distance I don't
think is gonna be merged I think that we
need to address what you're using it for
in end-to-end longitudinal and we just
need to make we just need to make open
pilot better to the point that you don't
need that we do calculate gaze direction
with the front camera that is part of
how our stuff works is anyone working on
flex rating not a comma because a bunch
of external people join the discord can
a cop give you a ticket absolutely
you're completely liable at all times
and always remember guys pay attention
um
UI button to tag grid events yeah as you
dance that he's off having down a degree
worth it I think most of the contents
available for free get opted into long
control maybe you guys look into it if
it's good that I would consider merging
I live in San Diego that's what common
AI is Lane hugging like as a motorcycle
on the right side need to hug the left
lane man that's coming when we ship lane
list check out zero six five I think
it's actually gonna be much better um
walks when I missed your thing how many
FPS 20 fps we don't sell the harness in
parts one price one deal how smart was
our team mad smart
san diego's pretty cool people sleeping
a test was actually sneaky marketing it
might be the porn really was good for
get zero six five out yeah I got it I
got to go do that
Insurance is kind of boring but yeah
we'll probably have that installation
companies or dealerships dealerships but
if you want to be an installation
company you can actually do that right
now we have great bulk discounts on all
our products eta for lane list end of
the year or the lane hugging be
adjustable no it will not it'll just be
great stop signs and stoplights man will
later after Tesla ships them we'll look
into it
before Tesla ships them we're not gonna
look into it it's hard again it's easy
if you're way mo and you can map every
one of them but if you want to work at
every stoplight and stop sign in the
country Lance a lot harder but uh you
know the black panda has a
high-precision GPS so if we ever do ship
features like that you already got the
stuff you are going to need see how far
the Corolla can steer you got lock to
lock using joystick do ya the Corolla
torque is crazy Corolla is a super light
car and it's got like the same torque as
a rav4 we don't rent the server's we
bought them we got great prices on used
servers you sell your product in Panama
yes and it should absolutely work we
don't we cancelled the referral fee
program it didn't get more sales people
we're to hire more people who try to
port more cars probably not almost all
our cars are Toyota and Honda
but we'll get to him we got to make it
easier to port a car and this hardware
is a big step towards that do you go
spare time we're always working always
working bro I got tons of spare time
check my streams on Twitch does it work
well when it's driving on the left we
have something probably coming for
left-handed driving you won't be
disappointed if you find it I will say
that you can check out some of the
things but guys I'm already three
minutes overtime we're not hiring remote
what's the fanciest car with kama
installed no ecord is pretty nice high
trim Toyota Camrys pretty nice
what Lane the car is in yes absolutely
it's accurate to a meter what car ports
are left really much yeah we're to be
got them all Tesla Tesla Tesla Tesla
any Java damn position now we don't use
Java older come older Corolla and it's
gonna be a ton of work may
if you replace the steering column can
you put open pilot and Tesla yes and
people have done it checked the discord
um Genesis is nice and nicer with Opie
that's right oh genesis is it pretty
nice well that's actually not a bad
choice a bunch of Lexuses have it
Corolla doesn't have Android auto I know
I know
come back soon zero seven zero seven by
the end of the year Bentley GT support I
don't think so
alright guys thank you for joining the
final sales total is twenty eight
thousand nine hundred fourteen dollars
thank you all for joining get your order
in for common harness you're gonna love
it
$3.99 prices only go up you saw it here
thank you all for watching we'll take
one more look at the beautiful harness
Python is a dying language pythons girl
I'm mad fast and we're on Python three
now so it's great
alright see you all later bye-bye